[00:22.32]Dropped in a pit, nowhere to run!
[00:24.82]It's only you, a man with no gun
[00:27.68]In the distance a tunnel so dark
[00:30.03]Illuminated by one small spark!
[00:32.90]Metal scraping, no escaping!
[00:35.47]Furious sounds, death abound
[00:37.92]Running helplessly, you start to see
[00:40.66]It cannot be! The Slashing Machine!
[00:43.37]Lost in the sewers, nowhere to run!
[00:45.83]There is no hope! Your time is done!
[00:48.57]Metal clanging, blades clashing
[00:51.22]Mechanical death, takes your last breath!
[00:53.90]You!... Can't!...Run!, it's here! Sliced to bits!
[01:00.66]You!... Can't!... Hide!, cold steel! Sliced to bits!
[01:07.22]You!... Will!... Meet!, your death! Sliced to bits!
[01:14.71]
[01:24.35]Dropped in a pit, nowhere to run!
[01:26.87]It's only you, a man with no gun
[01:29.26]In the distance a tunnel so dark
[01:32.07]Illuminated by one small spark!
[01:34.84]Metal scraping, no escaping!
[01:37.27]Furious sounds, death abound
[01:39.83]Running helplessly, you start to see
[01:42.69]It cannot be! The Slashing Machine!
[01:45.41]Lost in the sewers, nowhere to run!
[01:47.97]There is no hope! Your time is done!
[01:50.51]Metal clanging, blades clashing
[01:53.25]Mechanical death, takes your last breath!
[01:55.95]You!... Can't!...Run!, it's here! Sliced to bits!
[02:02.54]You!... Can't!... Hide!, cold steel! Sliced to bits!
[02:09.04]You!... Will!... Meet!, your death!Sliced to bits!
[02:15.75]You!... Will!... Meet!, your death!Sliced to bits!
[02:22.17]You!... Will!... Meet!, your death!Sliced to bits!
[02:29.69]
[03:24.38]Flaming eyes, blades like a blender !
[03:26.86]Automaton demon, it does not surrender!
[03:29.36]Sharpened rotors, swinging razors!
[03:32.07]Evil weapons, barbed wire and lasers!
[03:34.67]You!... Can't!...Run!, it's here! Sliced to bits!
[03:41.79]You!... Can't!... Hide!, cold steel! Sliced to bits!
[03:47.95]You!... Will!... Meet!, your death! Sliced to bits!
[03:56.56]
